we got the scoop on the all-new couch
bed for this product review please make
sure to LIKE and subscribe to Sara scoop
com to get the scoop on all your
favorite things the couch bed is made of
high-density 30 per memory foam that
converts from a sofa to a mattress in
seconds you can choose from twin or
queen sized couch beds in three
different colors charcoal lime stone and
navy the color choices make the couch
bed great and easy to match to any rooms
color scheme the couch bed is the
perfect solution if you're looking for a
new piece of furniture for your office
if you don't have a ton of open room
this couch bed is perfect for just your
space the couch bed is very simple to
set up when it arrives the mattress is
folded into an air sealed casing inside
the box all you have to do is cut it
loose from the plastic casing and lay it
out flat on the floor the bed will
continue to expand to its full size for
the next 24 to 48 hours the box is not
too heavy to maneuver either with the
twin couch bed weighing only 47 pounds
and the queen-size bed weighing 70
pounds the couch but is perfect for a
college dorm room as it can transform
into a mattress to a Polish lounging
couch by effortlessly flipping over a
single panel its compact design makes it
easy to store against almost any wall so
you can maximize your floor space
something all college dorm rooms lack
you will also never get hot sleeping on
the couch bed they are infused with cool
gel for an optimal sleep temperature
keeping you cool throughout the night
even on a warm summer night however in
the winter you can still use a heating
pad and not worry about damage being
done to your couch bed another great
thing about the couch bed is that its
material is environmentally friendly and
contains no harmful chemicals in the
phone
it is completely pet and child safe
making it perfect for families with
children it is also a hundred percent
latex free so latex allergies are not an
issue the couch but has washable
interchangeable covers that make messes
and spills easy to clean up
you can keep your couch bed in a
children's playroom and know that it
won't get ruined if you do need to clean
your couch bed just simply spot clean it
with a mild detergent couch bed makes it
easy to afford their fantastic product
by offering 12 month interest very
financing and when you order every couch
bag comes with two free bamboo pillows
to stylize your couch bed although
unlikely if you should happen to have a
problem with your couch bed
they are warranted for 10 years this
allows you to easily file a claim and
arrangements will be made just for you
thank you so much for watching please
don't forget to go like him subscribe to
Sara scoot comm to get more scoop on all
your favorite things